// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "FIND NOUN: The Ganga River is long",
    answer: "Ganga River",
    options: [
      "Ganga River",
      "is",
      "long",
      " Ganga "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Where did Johnny go?",
    answer: "Johnny",
    options: [
      "Where",
      "Did",
      "Johnny",
      "Go"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
     question: "Chennai has cold weather",
    answer: "Chennai",
    options: [
      "Has",
      "Cold",
      "Chennai",
      "Weather"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Bala plays the violin",
    answer: "Bala",
    options: [
      "Violin",
      "Bala",
      "Plays",
      "The"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5, question: "This Desk is very small",
    answer: "Desk",
    options: [
      "Very",
      "Small",
      "This",
      "Desk"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 6,
 question: "My dog is quite Playful",
    answer: "Dog",
    options: [
      "Dog",
      "is",
      "quite",
      "My"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 7, question: "This book is quite boring",
    answer: "Book",
    options: [
      "This",
      "Book",
      "is",
      "quite"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 8, question: "Tom is German",
    answer: "Tom",
    options: [
      "Tom",
      "is",
      "German",
      "None"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 9, question: "This is the most comfortable bed",
    answer: "Bed",
    options: [
      "This",
      "most",
      "is",
      "Bed"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 10, question: "Harini sings song",
    answer: "Harini",
    options: [
      "sings",
      "song",
      "Harini",
      "None"
    ]
  },
];